<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software on Ankit Gupta</title>
    <link>https://ankitgta.github.io/tags/software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software on Ankit Gupta</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Ankit Gupta</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 12:16:06 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ankitgta.github.io/tags/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Blogs Collection</title>
      <link>https://ankitgta.github.io/posts/20200911-good-blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 12:16:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankitgta.github.io/posts/20200911-good-blogs/</guid>
      <description>Good Reads Collection Time to time I come across some really good, well-maintained and well-formatted blogs on the internet. This is a place to pin them:
Link  https://nibnalin.me/about/ https://5harath.com/#projects https://theangelphilosopher.com/home  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Reads Collection</title>
      <link>https://ankitgta.github.io/posts/20200908-good-reads/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 12:16:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankitgta.github.io/posts/20200908-good-reads/</guid>
      <description>Good Reads Collection Collecting good articles that I found over the period of time and small summaries about them.
Imposter Syndrome @ Amazon In this article, an Amazon employee confessed how he shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be hired at Amazon in the first place. He lacked a lot of technical and leadership skills. But over the period of 2 years, he grew himself to be a worthy SDE-2. He did it by collecting constructive feedback from his peers and reflecting on them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogging Begins!!</title>
      <link>https://ankitgta.github.io/posts/20200418-my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 12:16:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankitgta.github.io/posts/20200418-my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>First Post So I have been trying to start a blog for so long. Precisely 2 long years. Since I started working at Amazon. My rate of learning has gone through the roof. I like gathering new ideas. Researching on them and apply them to my day-to-day life.
In my humble opinion, this blog is a result of that only. I am a software engineer by profession. So, I am well aware of the fact to make something work through automation rather than just pushing out the door.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>